Register of the Jay Lovestone papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRINTED MATERIAL, 1911-1977 (Boxes 1-191)
  - Horup, Ellen, Spain, The Battlefield of Capitalism, undated
  - Houphouet-Boigny, Felix, Black Africa and the French Union, 1957 (Box 79)
  - Houser, George M., Whirlwind Tour, Mboya Visits the U.S., 1959
  - How Warsaw Fell, undated
  - Howe, Irving, Looking Forward, On the Nature of Communism and Relations With Communists, undated
  - Hron, Jiri, The Finger on the Trigger, 1961
  - Hsinhua News Agency, Selected Hsinhua News Items, 1966 July 25, October 3, October 17
  - Hughes, Elizabeth A., Living Conditions for Small-Wage Earners in Chicago, 1925
  - Human Events, 1950 June 14, 1956 May 12, 1958 February 24
  - Human Rights in U.S.S.R., 1974
  - Human Rights, the Dignity of Man, 1963
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.
    - Address by Honorable Hubert H. Humphrey, Vice President of the United States, United States Military Academy, 1966 June 8
    - The Case for a Fair Deal Labor Policy, 1949 June 10-14
  - Hungarian Freedom Fighter, 1958 July, 1960 January
  - The Hungarian Observer, 1952 January-February
  - Hungarian Trade Union News, 1969
  - Hungary
    - Figures About Hungary, circa 1960
    - Hungary and Russia, 1958
    - Hungary Under Soviet Rule IV, 1960
    - Opinion, Concerning the Representation of Hungary in the United Nations, undated
    - Three Years of Kadar, 1956-1959, undated
    - XXth Congress of the Hungarian Trade Unions, 1963
  - Hunsberger, Warren S., Japan, New Industrial Giant, 1971
  - Hunter, Robert E., The Soviet Dilemma in the Middle East, Part I: Problems of Commitment, Part II: Oil and the Persian Gulf, 1969
  - Huntley, James Robert, The NATO Story, undated
  - Huntz, Jack, Spotlight on Spain, undated
  - Huxley, Aldous, An Encyclopedia of Pacifism, 1937
  - Huyn, Hans Graf, Der Moskauer Vertrag vom 12. August 1970, undated
  - Hwang, Tien-chien, Failures of Mao Tze-tung's Dictatorship, 1949-1963
  - I-D Europa Informationen, 1973 May (Box 80)
  - IFBWW Bulletin, 1970-1971
  - IG Chemie Papier Keramik, Presse-dienst, 1968 August 21
  - ILB News Report (incomplete), 1957 June - 1958 January
  - ILO (International Labour Organization)
    - News, 1959 June, 1969 April
    - Press, 1970 June
    - Provisional Record, 1968, 1975
    - Report of the Director-General, 1962
  - IMF News, 1973 September
  - IPA Facts, 1966 October-November
  - IRIS (Industrial Research and Information Services, Ltd.)
    - IRIS News (incomplete), 1963 September - 1967 September
    - IRIS News Survey
      - The British "Left,", 1970 August
      - The Communist Party Today, 1966 August
      - Russian Oil, undated
      - Strikes in Britain, 1968 August
      - Trade Union Organization, 1967 August
      - The World Federation of Trade Unions, 1965 February
    - In Perspective, 1972 February
    - Incomes Policy, 1972 June
    - The TUC, 1972 December
    - Trade Unions and the E.E.C., 1973 February
  - I.S.D., Informazional Sindacalismo Democratico, 1970
  - ITF Newsletter, 1973 September
  - I.W.M.A. Press Service (International Working-Men's Association), 1940 August - 1941 February
  - Ihud Olami Information, 1960 January
  - Images secretes de la guerre, 1933 May
  - Impact of Dialectial Thought on Soviet Strategic Decisions, undated (Box 81)
  - An Impression of Russia, 1930
  - In Fact, 1950 June
  - In the Public Interest, 1974 August
  - In Your Hands, 1958
  - Independent Communist Labor League
    - American CP Writes Its Own Epitaph, 1938 May
    - In Memoriam: The Communist Party, circa 1937
    - Only Socialism Brings Peace, 1938
    - Where We Stand, 1938
    - Why Was Andres Nin Murdered?, undated
  - Independent India, 1941 June
  - Independent Labor League of America
    - Keep America Out of War, 1939
    - Vote Labor!, undated
    - Where We Stand, 1938
  - Independent Labour Party
    - Annual Report of the National Administrative Council, 1938
    - Come and See the Empire, undated
    - Final Agenda of Resolutions and Amendments, 1938
    - The I.L.P. and the 3rd International, 1920
    - They Did Not Pass, undated
  - Independent News, 1938 November 15, 1940 March-April
  - India
    - Ministry of External Affairs
      - India-China Border Problem, undated
      - Leading Events in India-China Relations, 1947-1962, undated
      - Nehru Writes to Heads of States, 1972
      - Nehru's Letter to Chou En-lai, 1962 November 14
      - World Press on Chinese Aggression, 1962
    - National Marxist Association of India, White Paper on Vijayawada, 1961
    - Publication Division
      - China's Fraudulent Peace Offensive, 1962
      - Menace to India's Freedom, 1962
      - A Nation Aroused, 1962
    - Radical Democratic Party, Principles of Radical Democracy, 1947
    - Swatantra Party, You're in the Soup All Right, undated
  - Indian National Trade Union Congress, Ninth Annual Conference, 1958 January
  - Indian Worker, 1958 October 6
  - Indo-American Technical Cooperation, 1952-1956
  - An Industrial and Labor Relation Report Card, 1968 April
  - Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1974-1975
  - Industrial News (incomplete), 1940 May - 1941 April, 1968 July 24-25
  - Industrial Relations Newsletter, 1956 Spring
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, Intepreting the Labor Movement, 1952
  - Industriegewerkschaft Bau-Steine-Erden (Box 82)
    - Teilnehmerverzeichnis, 6. ordentlicher Gewerkschaftstag, Berlin, 1963
    - Who We Are, What We Do, undated
  - Industriekurier, 1955 March 3
  - Information Briefing, 1974
  - Information Bulletin, Organ of the Serbian National Committee, 1963 April 6
  - Information Bulletin, World Marxist Review (incomplete), 1966-1970
  - Information Bulletin About Yugoslavia, 1957 April
  - Information et riposte, 1951 November 15
  - Informations europeennes, 1957 May 2
  - Inglis, David R., Testing and Taming of Nuclear Weapons, 1960
  - The Innsbruck Story, 1951
  - The Insider's Newsletter, 1962 March 12
  - Institute for American Strategy, The Soviet Economic Challenge, 1959
  - Institute for Consumer Education
    - Chain Stores-Pro and Con, 1940
    - Defense and the Consumer, 1941
  - Institute for International Youth Affairs, New Features, 1962 July
  - The Institute for Propaganda Analysis, The Fine Art of Propaganda, 1939
  - Institute for Strategic Studies
    - The Communist Bloc and the Free World, The Military Balance, 1960
    - Multinational Enterprise and National Security, 1971
    - Soviet Attitudes to SALT, 1971
    - The Soviet Union and the NATO Powers: The Military Balance, undated
    - Strategic Survey, 1968
  - Institute for the Study of the USSR (Box 83)
    - Analysis of Current Developments in the Soviet Union (incomplete)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 83)
      - 1962-1963
      - 1963-1964
      - 1964-1965
      - 1965-1966 (Box 84)
      - 1966-1967
      - 1967
      - 1968
      - 1969
    - Bulletin, 1960 August, 1969 October (Box 85)
    - Soviet Affairs Analysis Service (incomplete)
      - 1959-1960
      - 1960-1961
      - 1961-1962
    - XXII Party Congress
  - Institute of American Business, Muscle Shoals, 1922 (Box 86)
  - Institute of International Education, News Bulletin, 1943 October
  - Institute of International Labor Research, Independence for All Nations, undated
  - Institute of Workers Education
    - Collective Bargaining by S. R. Mohan Das, 1964
    - Problems of Indian Trade Unionism and Labour Relations by Van Dusen Kennedy, 1964
  - Les intellectuels communistes et le culte de Staline, 1962
  - Inter-American Labor Bulletin, 1961 September-October
  - Inter-American Trade Union Economic Conference, Report, 1961 August
  - Intercontinental Press, 1968 June, 1970 January, March, November
  - International Affairs, 1963 August, October, 1969 September, 1974 May
  - International African Service Bureau, The West Indies To-Day, undated
  - International Association of Machinists
    - Bulletin, 1947 July, 1949 September, 1951 November
    - Thoughts of a Trade Unionist, undated
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters
    - Beck Reports on Europe, 1954
    - News Service, 1969 May 26-27
  - International Bulletin of the Trade Union and Working Class Press, 1959 November, 1960 August, November
  - International Bureau for Revolutionary Socialist Unity, A New Hope for World Socialism, 1938
  - International Center, Postwar Problems of the Pacific and World Organization, 1944
  - International Centre of Free Trade Unionists in Exile
    - Analysis and Synthesis: Women in Eastern Europe, 1956 June
    - International Communism: Change or Conflict?, 1965 July
    - The International Class Struggle (incomplete), 1936-1937
  - International Commission Against Concentration Camp Practices, Monthly Information Bulletin, 1955 August-November (Box 87)
  - International Commission of Jurists
    - African Conference on the Rule of Law, 1961
    - The Berlin Wall, A Defiance of Human Rights, 1962
    - Bulletin, 1956 June, 1959 August, 1962 May, 1966 June
    - Cuba and the Rule of Law, 1962
    - The Dynamic Aspects of the Rule of Law in the Modern Age, 1965
    - The Question of Tibet and the Rule of Law, 1959
    - The Rule of Law in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1958
    - The Rule of Law in Italy, 1958
    - Spain and the Rule of Law, 1962
  - The International Committee for Political Prisoners, 1927
  - International Communist Opposition, The Road to Communism, 1934 May-July, Fall, 1935 January, Spring
  - International Conciliation
    - ECA and the Paradox of African Cooperation, 1970 November
    - Issues Before the Thirteenth General Assembly, 1958 September
  - Issues Before the Twelfth General Assembly, 1957 September
  - The Law on Bulgarian Nationality by Theodore Geshkoff, 1928 May
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) (Box 88)
    - African Labour News (incomplete), 1962-1972 (Box 88)
    - Afro Reseach Bulletin, 1964 November
    - Asian Trade Union College, 1952-1954
    - Economic and Social Bulletin, 1969 July-August, 1971 March-April, 1974 July-August
    - Features (incomplete), 1965 May - 1972 August
    - For Bread, Peace and Freedom, 1949
    - Foreign Investment in Economically Underdeveloped Countries, 1959
    - Free Labour World (incomplete), 1953 April - 1973 December
    - The ICFTU and the Workers of Morocco, 1956
    - Information Bulletin (incomplete), 1952 December - 1962 November
    - International Free Trade Union News, 1949 November, 1951 September
    - International Trade Union News (incomplete), 1963-1977
    - The Need for a Dynamic World Economy, 1959 (Box 89)
    - News (incomplete), 1951-1959
    - The Permanent Struggle of the Free Trade Union Movement Against Latin American Dictatorships, 1960
    - Press and Radio Service (incomplete), 1962-1969
    - Radio Service (incomplete), 1965-1959
    - The Role of Trade Unions in the Economic Development of Europe, 1966
    - S.O.S. Berlin, undated
    - Spotlight (incomplete), 1952-1960
    - World Congress, 1951-1959
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions - Asian Regional Organization (Box 90)
    - Asian Labour News, 1965 July 15
    - ICFTU-ARO Bulletin (incomplete), 1956-1958
    - Newsletter, 1965 September 4
    - United Front Ministry and Trade Unions in West Bengal, 1967
  - International Congress on Mental Health, 1948
  - International Credit Bank, Geneva, Quarterly Review, No. 1, 1973
  - International Documentation and Information Centre (INTERDOC)
    - Activities of the Communist World Organizations, 1968
    - Africa in the Light of Soviet-Russian Publications, 1969 July-September
    - East-West Contacts, 1968 June, 1969 April-June
    - East-West Contacts in Practice, 1965 April
    - National Views on Neutralism and East-West Detente, 1969
    - Notes on Communist and Communist-Sponsored Activities as Reported By Communist Sources, 1968 May, June, October, 1969 May
    - The Position of Women in the Soviet Union, 1969
    - Processes of Consolidation and Destruction in Czechoslovakia, 1969
    - The Psychological Situation in East Germany, 1969
    - Red China, 1969 March-April
    - Religion and Church in the Communist Orbit, 1966-1969
    - The Union of Polish Pioneers, 1969
  - International Federation of Petroleum and Chemical Workers, Discord, 1967
  - International Institute for Peace, Economic Aspects of Disarmament, 1963
  - International Journal, 1958 Winter-1959
  - International Juridical Association, Curbing the Courts, 1937
  - International Labour Conference, Delegations and Secretariat, 1963
  - International Labour News, 1965 January
  - International Labour Office (ILO)
    - Activities of the ILO, 1968
    - Approaches to Social Security, 1942
    - The Compensation of War Victims, 1940
    - Forced Labour, 1968
    - Industrial Safety Survey, 1942
    - Little Stories of Other Countries, 1924
    - Manual on Procedures Relating to International Labour Conventions and Recommendations, 1965
    - A New Era, 1944
    - Provisional Record, 1969 (Box 91)
    - Reports, 1945-1974
    - War Time Transference of Labour in Great Britain, 1942
  - International Labour Review, 1960 July, 1970 January
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
    - American Labor Faces the Future, undated
    - Campaign Liberature - Presidential Election, 1944
    - A Democratic Foreign Policy for the United States, 1947
    - A Fighting Program for the Dressmakers, undated
    - Handbook of Trade Union Methods, 1937
    - How to Start Classes, 1937
    - Justice, 1956 February 1, 1975 October 15-November 1
    - Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - Mooney and Billings Must be Freed!, 1936
    - 1919-1944, Local 89 ILGWU Jubillee
    - The Position of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union in Relation to CIO and AFL, 1934-1938
    - Reports, Proceedings
      - Twenty-First Convention, 1932
      - Twenty-Sixth Convention, 1947
      - Twenty-Seventh Convention, 1950
      - Twenty-Eighth Convention, 1953
      - Thirtieth Convention, 1959
      - Thirty-Second Convention, 1965
      - Thirty-Third Convention, 1968
      - Thirty-Fourth Convention, 1971
      - Thirty-Fifth Convention, 1974
    - The Story of the I.L.G.W.U., 1935 (Box 93)
    - The Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., 1934
    - Win the Cold War, Preserve the Peace, 1950
  - International Ladies' Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, Reports to the Fourth and Fifth Conventions, 1942, 1946
  - The International League for the Rights of Man, The Rights of Man and the Wrongs of States, 1965
  - International Longshoremen's Association
    - The President Reports, 1971
    - Report and Recommendations of Special Mission to Nigeria, 1970
  - International Metalworkers' Federation, Resolutions, 1974
  - International Organizations, 1959, 1961
  - International Peasant Union, 1956 March, 1958 April
  - International Peasant Union, The Failure of Communist Agriculture, 1963
  - International Press Correspondence, Material on the Russian Question, 1926
  - International Rescue Committee, Annual Report, 1963
  - International Review Service, Representation of China in the United Nations, 1957
    - The Arms Race, 1957
    - Representation of China in the United Nations, 1957
  - International Security: The Military Aspect, 1958
  - International Service of Information Foundation, General Report, 1951
  - International Trade Union Conference, European Recovery Programme, 1948
  - International Transport Workers' Federation, Press Reports, 1944 November, 1946 May, 1974 March, 1951 December
  - International Transport Workers' Journal, 1944 September-October, 1958 March
  - International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Association, News Bulletin (incomplete), 1968-1972 (Box 94)
  - The International Union of Socialist Youth, Communist-Trained Youth Revolts Against Communism, 1957
  - International Union United Automobile Workers of America, Proceedings, 1939
  - Internationale Arbeiter-Hilfe, 1925
  - International Vereinigung kommunistischer Opposition
    - Internationale Nachrichten, 1931 July
    - Der Krieg und die kommunistische Internationale, 1937
    - Zur Krise in der Sowjetunion, 1937
    - Der Zusammenbruch der Weimarer Republik und was weiter?, undated
  - Internationale Nachrichten, 1931 July
  - Internationaler Bund freier Gewerkschaften, Die tschechoslowakischen Gewerkschaften, 1870-1970
  - The Interpreter
    - 1955-1963
    - 1964-1976 (Box 95)
  - Iraq News Agency, 1963
  - Ireland, Ireland's Right to Unity, undated
  - The Iron and Steel Trades Confederation, Report of Delegation to the U.S.S.R., 1945
  - Ise, Joh, Our Vanishing Oil Resources, 1929
  - The Islamic Center, Islam and Humane Tenets, undated
  - Israel
    - Embassy, Washinton, D.C., Policy Background, The "Imminent War" Thesis and the Mideast Reality, 1969
    - The Histadrut: The General Federation of Jewish Labor in Israel, circa 1958
    - Information Services, The Record of Aggression, 1967
    - Policy Statements, 1970
  - Israel Digest, 1955 December 23
  - Israel Labor Bulletin, 1956
  - Israel Labour News, 1949 October 5
  - Israel Labour Party, What Mapai Stands For, 1959
  - Issues and Answers, UN Membership for Mao, 1966
  - Issues and Studies, 1965 February
  - Italian Affairs, 1954 September
  - Italian-American Labor Council, Celebration Luncheon, 1958 December 20
  - Italy. Federazione Italiana dei Sindacati Postelgrafonici, Il Congresso, 1944
  - Italy Against Fascism, 1942
  - Italy's Struggle for Liberation, 1944
  - Izuka, Ichiro, The Truth About Communism in Hawaii, 1947
  - JTA Daily News Bulletin, 1968 March (Box 96)
  - JTUC Report (incomplete), 1956-1963
  - J. Henry Schroder and Company, Quarterly Review of International Conditions, 1931 May, August
  - Jaffe, Grace M., Le mouvement ouvrier a Paris, undated
  - Jain, Girilal, Chinese "Panchesheela" Chinese, 1956
  - Janes, George Milton, The Control of Strikes in American Trade Unions, 1916
  - Japan
    - Ministry of Foreign Affairs
      - The Japan of Today, 1963
      - Working Conditions in Japan, 1960
    - Ministry of Labor
      - Japanese Women Today, 1964
      - Labor Administration of Japan, 1964
  - Japan, 1964
  - Japan as an Export Market, 1972
  - Japan Federation of Employers' Associations
    - Conditions of Labour Economy in Japan, 1970
    - An Outline of the Japan Federation of Employers' Association, 1970
  - The Japan Institute of Labor (Box 97)
    - Directory of National Unions in Japan, 1965
    - Japan Labor Bulletin (incomplete), 1962-1975
    - Japan's Labor Statistics, 1967
    - Labor Relations in the Asian Countries, 1967
  - Japan Labour Movement, 1973 January
  - Japan Productivity Center
    - Productivity Drive in Japan, 1962
    - The Productivity Movement in Japan, 1964
  - Japan Report (incomplete), 1960-1975
  - Japanese Communist Party, The Program and Contract of the Japanese Communist Party, undated
  - Japanese Confederation of Labour
    See also: listing under Domei News.
    - Constitution, 1964
    - Democratic Trade Union Movement in Japan, 1964
  - Japanese Economic Mission to the United States, Report, 1964
  - Javits, Benjamin A., and Leon H. Keyserling, The World Development Corporation, 1959 (Box 98)
  - Jenks, M., The Communist Nucleus, What It Is--How It Works, 1928
  - The Jerusalem Post, 1970 July 27
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jews Behind the Iron Curtain, 1949
  - Jewish Newsletter, 1958 September 22, 1961 August 7
  - Jews and the Jewish People, Collected Materials From the Soviet Daily and Periodical Press, 1963
  - Jews in Eastern Europe, 1968 March
  - Jobs for Veterans Report (incomplete), 1975-1976
  - Joensson, Algot, Organized Labor and Democracy in Germany, 1949
  - Joffe, Ellis, Party and Army, Professionalism and Political Control in the Chinese Officer Corps, 1949-1965
  - John XXII, Pope, Pacem in Terris, 1963
  - The John Birch Society, Bulletin, 1965 July
  - John Herling's Labor Letter (incomplete), 1965-1974
  - Johnson, Alvin, and Ernest Hamburger, The Economic Problem of Germany, 1946
  - The Johnson Foundation, Viet Nam, 1964
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., Public Order Based on Equal Justice, 1967
  - Johnson, Priscilla, The Regime and the Intellectuals: A Window on Party Politics, circa 1963
  - Jordanian Operational Orders for the Destruction of Israeli Settlements and Killing All Persons in Them, 1967
  - Joshua, Wynfred, Soviet Penetration Into the Middle East, 1970
  - Jukic, Ilija, Tito Between East and West, 1961
  - Jutro Polski, 1958 February 22 (Box 99)
  - K.D.K. Information (incomplete), 1972-1976
  - Kaganowitsch, L. M., Der organisatorische Aufbau der RKP, 1925
  - Kalandra, Zavis, O Spanelskou Revoluci, 1936
  - Kalnins, Bruno, Ist die Sowjetunion ein sozialistischer Staat?, 1948
  - Kamath, H. V., Communist China Colonizes Tibet, Invades India, 1959
  - Kamp, Joseph P., Join the C.I.O and Help Build a Soviet America, 1937
  - Kampfgruppe Gegen Unmenschlichkeit, Die Jugend der Sowjetzone in Deutschland, 1955
  - Kantor, Harry
    - The Development of Accion Democratica de Venezuela, 1959
    - The Development of Democratic Government in Latin America, 1960
    - Governing Our Metropolitan Communities, 1958
    - Public Finances Parties, 1958
  - Kardelj, Edvard, The International Scene and the Yugoslav Position, 1950
  - Karsh, Bernard, Kawada, Hisashi, and Levine, Solomon B., Comparative Research in Industrial Relations: Three Papers, 1966
  - Katz, Amrom H., The Myth of Overkill, 1964
  - Kavanagh, Denis, J., Answer to Skeptics, 1943
  - Kavcic, Stane, Self-Government in Yugoslavia, 1961
  - Keating, Charles H., Jr., The Report That Shocked the Nation, 1971
  - Kelley, Douglas C., Africa in Paperbacks, 1960
  - Kennan, George F., Japanese Security and American Policy, 1964 October
  - Keracher, John
    - Crime, Its Causes and Consequences, 1937
    - Economics for Beginners, 1935
    - The Head-Fixing Industry, 1935
    - How the Gods Were Made, 1929
    - Producers and Parasites, 1935
    - Proletarian Lessons, undated
    - Why Unemployment?, 1935
  - Kerala Liberation Movement, Tempest In Kerala, undated (Box 100)
  - Kerala Pradesh Congress Committee, True Picture of the Situation in Kerala, 1958
  - Kerala School Managers' Association, Kerala, The Present Textbooks Memorial, 1958
  - Kerr, Clark, and Siegel, Abraham, The Interindustry Propensity to Strike: An International Comparison, 1954
  - Keys, Donald F., Human Rights: Present and Future, 1968
  - Keyserling, Leon H., Taxation of Whom and For What, 1969
  - Khatib, M. A., I.C.F.T.U. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Asian Regional Conference, Bread, Fredom, Peace, 1951
  - Khrushchev, N. S.
    - Disarmament--The Way to Secure Peace and Friendship Between Nations, 1960 January
    - Expose the Manoeuvres of Reaction, 1960
    - Freedom and Independence for all Colonial Peoples, 1960
    - Verbatim Report of Two Interviews Granted to American Newspaper Men, 1957
  - Kingdon, Frank, That Man in the White House, 1944
  - Kintner, William R., The Prudent Case for Safeguard, 1969
  - Kintner, William R., and Robert L. Pfaltzbraff, Jr., Soviet Military Trends: Implications for U.S. Security, 1971
  - Kirshbaum, Louis, Justice for Organized Workers, undated
  - Kiselev, K. V., Certain Results of the Work of the United Nations Organizations, 1946
  - Kissinger, Henry
    - Coalition Diplomacy in a Nuclear Age, 1964
    - For an Atlantic Confederacy, 1961
    - Strains on the Alliance, 1963
    - The Unsolved Problems of European Defense, 1962
  - Kithima, A. R., La doctrine generale du syndicalisme congolais, 1960
  - Kleczkowski, Stefan, Poland's First 100,000, undated
  - Kleinpaul, Rudolf, Deutsches Fremdworterbuch, 1937
  - Klotzner, Ottoman, Sowjet-Russlands wahres Gesicht, undated
  - Kloosterboer, W., Involuntary Labour Since the Abolition of Slavery, 1960